

import '../c_quiz.dart';

List<QuizS> cQuestionAnswer = [
  QuizS(
      question: "Who invented C Language.?",
      answer: "Dennis Ritchie",
      option1: "Charles Babbage",
      option2: "Grahambel",
      option3: "Dennis Ritchie",
      option4: "Steve Jobs"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C Language is a successor to which language.?",
      answer: "B Language",
      option1: "FORTRAN",
      option2: "D Language",
      option3: "BASIC",
      option4: "B Language"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C is a which level language.?",
      answer: "High Level",
      option1: "Low Level",
      option2: "High Level",
      option3: "Low + High",
      option4: "None"),
  QuizS(
      question: "Low level language is .?",
      answer: " Difficult to understand and readability is questionable.",
      option1: "Human readable like language.",
      option2: "language with big program size.",
      option3: "language with small program size.",
      option4: " Difficult to understand and readability is questionable."),
  QuizS(
      question: "High level language is a .?",
      answer: "Human readable like language.",
      option1: "Human readable like language.",
      option2: "language with small program size.",
      option3: "language with big program size.",
      option4:
      "language which is difficult to understand and not human readable."),
  QuizS(
      question: """Which program outputs "Hello World.." .?""",
      answer: """main()
{
  printf("Hello World..");
}""",
      option1: """main()
      {
      scanf("Hello World..");
      }""",
      option2: """main()
      {
  printf("Hello World..");
}""",
      option3: """main()
{
  print("Hello World..");
}""",
      option4: """main()
{
  scan("Hello World..");
}"""),
  QuizS(
      question: "C is _______ type of programming language.?",
      answer: "Procedural",
      option1: "Object Oriented",
      option2: "Procedural",
      option3: "Bit level language",
      option4: "Functional"),
  QuizS(
      question: "What is the present C Language Standard.?",
      answer: "C11 ISO/IEC 9899:2011",
      option1: "C99 ISO/IEC 9899:1999",
      option2: "C11 ISO/IEC 9899:2011",
      option3: "C05 ISO/IEC 9899:2005",
      option4: "C10 ISO/IEC 9899:2010"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C language was invented in which laboratories.?",
      answer: "AT&T Bell Labs",
      option1: "Uniliver Labs",
      option2: "IBM Labs",
      option3: "AT&T Bell Labs",
      option4: "Verizon Labs"),
  QuizS(
      question: "BCPL Language is also called..?",
      answer: "None",
      option1: "C Language",
      option2: "B Language",
      option3: "D Language",
      option4: "None"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C language was invented to develop which Operating System.?",
      answer: "Unix",
      option1: "Android",
      option2: "Linux",
      option3: "Ubuntu",
      option4: "Unix"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C language was invented in the year.?",
      answer: "1972",
      option1: "1999",
      option2: "1978",
      option3: "1972",
      option4: "1990"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C language is used in the development of .?",
      answer: "All of the above",
      option1: "Databases",
      option2: "Graphic applications",
      option3: "Word Processors",
      option4: "All of the above"),
  QuizS(
      question: "A C program is a combination of.?",
      answer: "All of the above",
      option1: "Statements",
      option2: "Functions",
      option3: "Variables",
      option4: "All of the above"),
  QuizS(
      question: "Single Line Comment // is also called.?",
      answer: "All the above",
      option1: "C++ Style Comment",
      option2: "Java Style Comment",
      option3: "PHP Style Comment",
      option4: "All the above"),
  QuizS(
      question: " What is an Identifier in C Language.?",
      answer: "All the above.",
      option1: "Name of a Function or Variable",
      option2: "Name of a Macros",
      option3: "Name of Structure or Union",
      option4: "All the above."),
  QuizS(
      question: "What is the number of characters used to distinguish Identifier or Names of Functions and Global variables.?",
      answer: "31",
      option1: "31",
      option2: "32",
      option3: "33",
      option4: "28"),
  QuizS(
      question: "What is length of an Identifier that is unique for Non Global Variables and Non Function Names.?",
      answer: "63",
      option1: "32",
      option2: "63",
      option3: "64",
      option4: "68"),
  QuizS(
      question: "An Identifier can start with.?",
      answer: "Option A & Option B",
      option1: "Alphabet",
      option2: "Underscore ( _ ) sign",
      option3: "Any character that can be typed on a keyboard",
      option4: "Option A & Option B"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C Programs are used in .?",
      answer: "All the above.",
      option1: "Any Electronic device which works on some logic and Operating System.",
      option2: "Washing machine",
      option3: "Fridge, Microwave Ovens",
      option4: "All the above."),
  QuizS(
      question: "What are the types of Constants in C Language.?",
      answer: "",
      option1: "Primary Constants",
      option2: "Secondary Constants",
      option3: "Basic Constants and Advanced Constants",
      option4: "Primary Constants and Secondary Constants"),
  QuizS(
      question: " Find an integer constant.",
      answer: "34",
      option1: "3.145",
      option2: "34",
      option3: "125",
      option4: "None of the above"),
  QuizS(
      question: "Find a Floating Point constant.",
      answer: "All the above.",
      option1: "12.3E5",
      option2: "12e34",
      option3: "125.34857",
      option4: "All the above."),
  QuizS(
      question: "Find a Character constant.",
      answer: "All the above.",
      option1: "'A'",
      option2: "'1'",
      option3: r"'$'",
      option4: "All the above."),
  QuizS(
      question: "Number of Keywords present in C Language are .?",
      answer: "32",
      option1: "32",
      option2: "34",
      option3: "64",
      option4: "62"),
  QuizS(
      question: "Number of Keywords present in C Language are .?",
      answer: "32",
      option1: "32",
      option2: "34",
      option3: "64",
      option4: "62"),

  QuizS(
      question: "Who invented C Language.?",
      answer: "Dennis Ritchie",
      option1: "Charles Babbage",
      option2: "Grahambel",
      option3: "Dennis Ritchie",
      option4: "Steve Jobs"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C Language is a successor to which language.?",
      answer: "B Language",
      option1: "FORTRAN",
      option2: "D Language",
      option3: "BASIC",
      option4: "B Language"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C is a which level language.?",
      answer: "High Level",
      option1: "Low Level",
      option2: "High Level",
      option3: "Low + High",
      option4: "None"),
  QuizS(
      question: "Low level language is .?",
      answer: " Difficult to understand and readability is questionable.",
      option1: "Human readable like language.",
      option2: "language with big program size.",
      option3: "language with small program size.",
      option4: " Difficult to understand and readability is questionable."),
  QuizS(
      question: "High level language is a .?",
      answer: "Human readable like language.",
      option1: "Human readable like language.",
      option2: "language with small program size.",
      option3: "language with big program size.",
      option4:
      "language which is difficult to understand and not human readable."),
  QuizS(
      question: """Which program outputs "Hello World.." .?""",
      answer: """main()
{
  printf("Hello World..");
}""",
      option1: """main()
      {
      scanf("Hello World..");
      }""",
      option2: """main()
      {
  printf("Hello World..");
}""",
      option3: """main()
{
  print("Hello World..");
}""",
      option4: """main()
{
  scan("Hello World..");
}"""),
  QuizS(
      question: "C is _______ type of programming language.?",
      answer: "Procedural",
      option1: "Object Oriented",
      option2: "Procedural",
      option3: "Bit level language",
      option4: "Functional"),
  QuizS(
      question: "What is the present C Language Standard.?",
      answer: "C11 ISO/IEC 9899:2011",
      option1: "C99 ISO/IEC 9899:1999",
      option2: "C11 ISO/IEC 9899:2011",
      option3: "C05 ISO/IEC 9899:2005",
      option4: "C10 ISO/IEC 9899:2010"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C language was invented in which laboratories.?",
      answer: "AT&T Bell Labs",
      option1: "Uniliver Labs",
      option2: "IBM Labs",
      option3: "AT&T Bell Labs",
      option4: "Verizon Labs"),
  QuizS(
      question: "BCPL Language is also called..?",
      answer: "None",
      option1: "C Language",
      option2: "B Language",
      option3: "D Language",
      option4: "None"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C language was invented to develop which Operating System.?",
      answer: "Unix",
      option1: "Android",
      option2: "Linux",
      option3: "Ubuntu",
      option4: "Unix"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C language was invented in the year.?",
      answer: "1972",
      option1: "1999",
      option2: "1978",
      option3: "1972",
      option4: "1990"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C language is used in the development of .?",
      answer: "All of the above",
      option1: "Databases",
      option2: "Graphic applications",
      option3: "Word Processors",
      option4: "All of the above"),
  QuizS(
      question: "A C program is a combination of.?",
      answer: "All of the above",
      option1: "Statements",
      option2: "Functions",
      option3: "Variables",
      option4: "All of the above"),
  QuizS(
      question: "Single Line Comment // is also called.?",
      answer: "All the above",
      option1: "C++ Style Comment",
      option2: "Java Style Comment",
      option3: "PHP Style Comment",
      option4: "All the above"),
  QuizS(
      question: " What is an Identifier in C Language.?",
      answer: "All the above.",
      option1: "Name of a Function or Variable",
      option2: "Name of a Macros",
      option3: "Name of Structure or Union",
      option4: "All the above."),
  QuizS(
      question: "What is the number of characters used to distinguish Identifier or Names of Functions and Global variables.?",
      answer: "31",
      option1: "31",
      option2: "32",
      option3: "33",
      option4: "28"),
  QuizS(
      question: "What is length of an Identifier that is unique for Non Global Variables and Non Function Names.?",
      answer: "63",
      option1: "32",
      option2: "63",
      option3: "64",
      option4: "68"),
  QuizS(
      question: "An Identifier can start with.?",
      answer: "Option A & Option B",
      option1: "Alphabet",
      option2: "Underscore ( _ ) sign",
      option3: "Any character that can be typed on a keyboard",
      option4: "Option A & Option B"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C Programs are used in .?",
      answer: "All the above.",
      option1: "Any Electronic device which works on some logic and Operating System.",
      option2: "Washing machine",
      option3: "Fridge, Microwave Ovens",
      option4: "All the above."),
  QuizS(
      question: "What are the types of Constants in C Language.?",
      answer: "",
      option1: "Primary Constants",
      option2: "Secondary Constants",
      option3: "Basic Constants and Advanced Constants",
      option4: "Primary Constants and Secondary Constants"),
  QuizS(
      question: " Find an integer constant.",
      answer: "34",
      option1: "3.145",
      option2: "34",
      option3: "125",
      option4: "None of the above"),
  QuizS(
      question: "Find a Floating Point constant.",
      answer: "All the above.",
      option1: "12.3E5",
      option2: "12e34",
      option3: "125.34857",
      option4: "All the above."),
  QuizS(
      question: "Find a Character constant.",
      answer: "All the above.",
      option1: "'A'",
      option2: "'1'",
      option3: r"'$'",
      option4: "All the above."),
  QuizS(
      question: "Number of Keywords present in C Language are .?",
      answer: "32",
      option1: "32",
      option2: "34",
      option3: "64",
      option4: "62"),
  QuizS(
      question: "Number of Keywords present in C Language are .?",
      answer: "32",
      option1: "32",
      option2: "34",
      option3: "64",
      option4: "62"),

  QuizS(
      question: "Who invented C Language.?",
      answer: "Dennis Ritchie",
      option1: "Charles Babbage",
      option2: "Grahambel",
      option3: "Dennis Ritchie",
      option4: "Steve Jobs"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C Language is a successor to which language.?",
      answer: "B Language",
      option1: "FORTRAN",
      option2: "D Language",
      option3: "BASIC",
      option4: "B Language"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C is a which level language.?",
      answer: "High Level",
      option1: "Low Level",
      option2: "High Level",
      option3: "Low + High",
      option4: "None"),
  QuizS(
      question: "Low level language is .?",
      answer: " Difficult to understand and readability is questionable.",
      option1: "Human readable like language.",
      option2: "language with big program size.",
      option3: "language with small program size.",
      option4: " Difficult to understand and readability is questionable."),
  QuizS(
      question: "High level language is a .?",
      answer: "Human readable like language.",
      option1: "Human readable like language.",
      option2: "language with small program size.",
      option3: "language with big program size.",
      option4:
      "language which is difficult to understand and not human readable."),
  QuizS(
      question: """Which program outputs "Hello World.." .?""",
      answer: """main()
{
  printf("Hello World..");
}""",
      option1: """main()
      {
      scanf("Hello World..");
      }""",
      option2: """main()
      {
  printf("Hello World..");
}""",
      option3: """main()
{
  print("Hello World..");
}""",
      option4: """main()
{
  scan("Hello World..");
}"""),
  QuizS(
      question: "C is _______ type of programming language.?",
      answer: "Procedural",
      option1: "Object Oriented",
      option2: "Procedural",
      option3: "Bit level language",
      option4: "Functional"),
  QuizS(
      question: "What is the present C Language Standard.?",
      answer: "C11 ISO/IEC 9899:2011",
      option1: "C99 ISO/IEC 9899:1999",
      option2: "C11 ISO/IEC 9899:2011",
      option3: "C05 ISO/IEC 9899:2005",
      option4: "C10 ISO/IEC 9899:2010"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C language was invented in which laboratories.?",
      answer: "AT&T Bell Labs",
      option1: "Uniliver Labs",
      option2: "IBM Labs",
      option3: "AT&T Bell Labs",
      option4: "Verizon Labs"),
  QuizS(
      question: "BCPL Language is also called..?",
      answer: "None",
      option1: "C Language",
      option2: "B Language",
      option3: "D Language",
      option4: "None"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C language was invented to develop which Operating System.?",
      answer: "Unix",
      option1: "Android",
      option2: "Linux",
      option3: "Ubuntu",
      option4: "Unix"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C language was invented in the year.?",
      answer: "1972",
      option1: "1999",
      option2: "1978",
      option3: "1972",
      option4: "1990"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C language is used in the development of .?",
      answer: "All of the above",
      option1: "Databases",
      option2: "Graphic applications",
      option3: "Word Processors",
      option4: "All of the above"),
  QuizS(
      question: "A C program is a combination of.?",
      answer: "All of the above",
      option1: "Statements",
      option2: "Functions",
      option3: "Variables",
      option4: "All of the above"),
  QuizS(
      question: "Single Line Comment // is also called.?",
      answer: "All the above",
      option1: "C++ Style Comment",
      option2: "Java Style Comment",
      option3: "PHP Style Comment",
      option4: "All the above"),
  QuizS(
      question: " What is an Identifier in C Language.?",
      answer: "All the above.",
      option1: "Name of a Function or Variable",
      option2: "Name of a Macros",
      option3: "Name of Structure or Union",
      option4: "All the above."),
  QuizS(
      question: "What is the number of characters used to distinguish Identifier or Names of Functions and Global variables.?",
      answer: "31",
      option1: "31",
      option2: "32",
      option3: "33",
      option4: "28"),
  QuizS(
      question: "What is length of an Identifier that is unique for Non Global Variables and Non Function Names.?",
      answer: "63",
      option1: "32",
      option2: "63",
      option3: "64",
      option4: "68"),
  QuizS(
      question: "An Identifier can start with.?",
      answer: "Option A & Option B",
      option1: "Alphabet",
      option2: "Underscore ( _ ) sign",
      option3: "Any character that can be typed on a keyboard",
      option4: "Option A & Option B"),
  QuizS(
      question: "C Programs are used in .?",
      answer: "All the above.",
      option1: "Any Electronic device which works on some logic and Operating System.",
      option2: "Washing machine",
      option3: "Fridge, Microwave Ovens",
      option4: "All the above."),
  QuizS(
      question: "What are the types of Constants in C Language.?",
      answer: "",
      option1: "Primary Constants",
      option2: "Secondary Constants",
      option3: "Basic Constants and Advanced Constants",
      option4: "Primary Constants and Secondary Constants"),
  QuizS(
      question: " Find an integer constant.",
      answer: "34",
      option1: "3.145",
      option2: "34",
      option3: "125",
      option4: "None of the above"),
  QuizS(
      question: "Find a Floating Point constant.",
      answer: "All the above.",
      option1: "12.3E5",
      option2: "12e34",
      option3: "125.34857",
      option4: "All the above."),
  QuizS(
      question: "Find a Character constant.",
      answer: "All the above.",
      option1: "'A'",
      option2: "'1'",
      option3: r"'$'",
      option4: "All the above."),
  QuizS(
      question: "Number of Keywords present in C Language are .?",
      answer: "32",
      option1: "32",
      option2: "34",
      option3: "64",
      option4: "62"),
  QuizS(
      question: "Number of Keywords present in C Language are .?",
      answer: "32",
      option1: "32",
      option2: "34",
      option3: "64",
      option4: "62"),
];
